24小时
第三季  第五集
前情提要
出了什么事?
What's wrong?
他会在辩论中提及你的前夫
He's bringing your ex-husband into this debate.
证监会对他的调查
The SEC's investigation into his company.
那就用事实迎战基勒的谎言
Then face Keeler's lie with the truth and trust that the people
相信人民能够明辨是非
will be able to tell the difference.
杰克 出了什么事? 托尼呢?
Jack, what's going on? Where's Tony?
他中枪了
He's been shot.
-严重吗?  -伤口在颈部
-How bad?  -He was hit in the neck.
他还活着 正送往医院
He's still alive, they're getting him to the hospital now.
托尼不在 你就是总指挥
With Tony down, you're in command.
把拉姆·萨拉扎送到范奈斯水库
Deliver Ramon Salazar to the Van Nuys dam.
打这个电话的人控制着凯尔 辛格勒的一举一动
Whoever sent this message is controlling Kyle Singer's movements.
病毒散播前 我们有两小时时间找他
We have two hours to find him before they release the virus.
你干了什么勾当凯尔?
What are you into Kyle?
今天警察去了我家
These cops, they came to my apartment today
他们说... 有人利用我
and they were saying something about... using me to,
把一种病毒带到了这个国家
to bring some weird disease into the country.
病毒...?
A disease...?
快跑! 快! 我什么都没做!
Go! Run! I didn't do anything, man!
不! 住手!
No! Stop!
-你要去见萨拉扎?  -是的
-You're going to see Salazar?  -Yeah.
我爸说审问他 是浪费时间
My dad said questioning him was a waste of time.
不 坐在这里等才是浪费时间
No. Sitting around here is a waste of time.
金 帮我做一份囚犯转移文件
Kim, I need you to generate a prisoner transfer document.
做来干嘛?
What's this about?
我要转移拉姆·萨拉扎
I need to move Ramon Salazar.
这是最高批准 反恐局所有人都不能知道
This has top priority clearance. No one at CTU is supposed to know.
要么我交出拉姆·萨拉扎
Either I hand over Ramon Salazar
要么他兄弟散播病毒
or his brother will release the virus.
我知道你不会做出选择
I understand that this is an impossible choice.
我有另一个主意
I have another option for you to consider.
把拉姆·萨拉扎劫出狱 交给他兄弟
Ramon Salazar would be broken out of prison and delivered to him.
听起来不错 杰克 谁去劫萨拉扎?
Sounds like quite a plan, Jack, but who'll break Salazar out?
我去
I will, sir.
这是我最后的任务
This would be my last assignment.
如果你表现得好 拉姆 我就带你出去
If you play this cool, Ramon, you're walking out of here with me.
解除监狱封锁 快
Open the cell blocks now.
走吧 快!
Let's go. Move!
各位东部的朋友 晚上好
Good evening to those of you on the east coast
各位西部的朋友 下午好
and good afternoon to those of you in the west.
欢迎参加总统帕默尔与参议员约翰 基勒
Welcome to first of three debates between President Palmer
三场辩论的第一场
and Senator John Keeler.
辩论开始时
We'll begin tonight
是两分钟的开场陈述 然后是第一个提问
with a two minute opening statement followed by the first question
第一个问题由总统大卫·帕默尔来回答
which will go to President David Palmer
这是经过刚才在后台抛硬币决定的
as decided by a coin flip backstage just moments ago.
感觉怎样?
How're you feeling?
会是医疗问题还是私人问题?
Is that a medical question or a personal one?
都是
Both.
我很好
I'm fine.
辩论程序是由双方
That will be conducted within formats of rules agreed to by each member of the debate
共同制定的
and by the two campaigns.
现在 有请候选人上台
Now we will bring to the stage the candidates.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎参议员约翰 基勒
Senator John Keeler.
大卫 很抱歉你必须应对我前夫的谎言
David, I'm sorry you have to deal with my ex-husband's lies.
没关系
It's alright.
真相站在我们这边
We have the truth on our side.
女士们先生们 欢迎总统大卫·帕默尔
Ladies and gentlemen, President David Palmer.
谢谢 约翰 祝你今晚好运
Thank you, John. Good luck tonight.
女士们先生们 参议员基勒
Ladies and gentlemen, Senator Keeler.
晚上好
Good evening.
我盼望能够
I'm looking forward to
讨论一些关键性的问题...
discussing some of the critical issues...
我给你信号
When I tell you to,
你就用枪打我
you start fighting with me over the gun.
我会把两个警卫引过来
I gotta try and pull two guards off the main corridor.
好 他们来了
Okay. They're coming.
救命! 救命! 救命!
Help! Help! Help!
别打了!
That's enough!
穿上他的制服和头盔!
Put on his uniform and helmet now!
把你的人分成几组
Split up your men.
每个安全出口一组
I want a team at every security.
不 杰克和萨拉扎在东区某个地方
No, Jack and Salazar are somewhere on east block.
把人手都安排到那儿
You need to put your men over there.
我控制着监狱 对付你搭档不在话下
I got to control this prison, your partner is not my only problem.
典狱长 今天他就是问题
Warden, today he is.
把他和萨拉扎抓起来 但必须活捉
He and Salazar need to be contained and they need to be kept alive.
你要我重新部署人手?
You want me to redeploy my men?
那我要搞清楚 这次恐怖威胁的真实性
Then I need to know how real this terrorist threat is.
过来
Come here.
拉姆·萨拉扎的兄弟称要在人群中 散播致命病毒
Ramon Salazar's brother will spread a deadly virus into the population
除非我们毫发无损地释放他
unless we release him unharmed.
如果我们拒绝 会有成千上万的人死去
If we don't the death toll will be in the hundreds of thousands.
我是典狱长米切尔 战术分队5 向控制中心汇报
This is Warden Mitchell. Tactical unit five, report to control center.
你们现在由埃德蒙兹探员指挥
You're now under the command of agent Edmunds.
谢谢
Thank you.
-喂?  -蔡斯 我是米歇尔
-Yeah?  -Chase, it's Michelle.
你那儿出了什么事?
What the hell is going on over there?
杰克想把萨拉扎弄出监狱
Jack tried to bring Salazar out of prison.
-引发了一场骚乱  -什么?
-He started a riot.  -What?
我想这是他的计策 他想把他交给赫克托
I think in his own twisted way he thinks he's gonna deliver him to Hector
从而阻止病毒散播
and stop the virus from being released.
可他会因此送命 更别说萨拉扎了
Well he's gonna get himself killed not to mention Salazar.
我知道
I know.
我在尽力保护他
I know, I'm trying to protect him.
凯尔 辛格勒找到了吗?
What about Kyle Singer?
快找到他的位置了
We're getting close to locating him.
米歇尔 找到了马上通知我
Michelle as soon as you do, call me.
如果杰克知道我们找到了病毒携带者 他会把萨拉扎带回来
If Jack knows we got the carrier of the virus he'll give Salazar back.
我们正集中全力查找 蔡斯
We got everyone working on it Chase.
-会找到他的  -好
-We'll find him.  -Okay.
对不起 琳达
I'm sorry, Linda.
我会死吗?
Am I gonna die?
说不清楚...
It depends...
如果他们及时找到我们
if they find us in time.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
政府的人...
The guy from the government...
他告诉我爸 我还有一些时间...
He told my dad that I had a couple of more hours before I...
才会具有传染性
Before I become contagious.
那时他们会找到我们的
Maybe they'll find us by then.
你会没事的
You'll be okay.
嗯...
Yeah...
可能吧
maybe.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
这里应该有电线
There must be some wires in here.
你用电线干嘛?
What do you need wire for?
救你出去
To get you out of this.
亚当 看这个
Adam. Look at this.
卡尔特兰服务器上的图像
Got it from a Caltrans server.
商场附近的交通摄像机
Traffic camera, right near the mall.
你看
Look at that.
蓝衫 不正是凯尔 辛格勒穿的吗?
It's a blue shirt. Isn't that what Kyle Singer was wearing?
对
Yeah.
可以进一步分析 发到我电脑上来
I think there's enough to enhance. Release it to my screen.
好
Got it.
-金  -嗯
-Kim.  -Yes.
我想和你谈一下
I need you a second.
收到了吗?
You got this?
-嗯  -很好
-Yeah.  -Alright.
出了什么事?
Is something wrong?
知道监狱发生的事吗?
You haven't been following what's going on at the prison, have you?
不知道 我和亚当一直在找辛格勒
No, Adam and I have been working on finding Singer.
怎么了?
Why, what is it?
你爸想把萨拉扎劫出狱
Your dad's trying to break out Salazar.
啊?
What?
是 他还没成功 但他擅自行事
Yeah, he's not out yet but he's acting on his own authority.
他想用武力把萨拉扎带出监狱
He's trying to remove Salazar by force.
我不明白你说的"用武力"
I don't understand what you mean "by force".
他引发监狱骚动 想趁混乱逃掉
Looks like he started a prison riot to cover the escape.
他为什么这么做?
Why is he doing this?
我们也想知道
That's what we're trying to figure out.
你最近一次跟他联系是什么时候?
When's the last time you heard from him?
半小时前
About a half hour ago.
他要我签一份拉姆·萨拉扎的转移令
He asked me to issue a transfer order
并给了我密码
for Ramon Salazar and he gave me a password.
你做了?
And you did it?
是 他说萨拉扎需要转移
Yeah, he said that Salazar needed to be moved.
但你现在又告诉我事情是假的?
But now you're telling me this isn't true?
对 金 很抱歉 你爸对你说谎了
No, Kim. I'm sorry. Your dad lied to you.
他为什么那么做?
Why would he do that?
因为他知道 叫其它人做这件事
Because he knew if he asked anybody else
都会知道这样做违规了
they would know he was violating protocol.
他会怎样?
What's gonna happen to him?
我们正在找他
We're gonna try to find him.
最好的解决办法就是找到凯尔 辛格勒
The best way out of this whole situation is to find Kyle Singer.
这样你爸就会交出萨拉扎
Then your dad will give up Salazar.
快去工作 帮助亚当
So go back to work, help Adam.
好的
Yeah, sure.
安全了
We're clear.
在核查人数之前 我们得找到武装人员的入口
We gotta find all their forces through one entrance to keep the personnel count.
肯定有别的出口 杰克
There must be another way, Jack.
有是有 但被囚犯控制了
There is, but the prisoners have taken control.
我们必须冲破重围
We're gonna have to fight our way through them.
准备
Get ready.
揍他们
Hit them up.
快
Come on.
来 让他们站起来
Come on. Get them on their feet.
快走 快走!
Come on, let's go, let's go!
快走 快!
Move, move it!
我们走!
Let's go!
别开枪!
Hold your fire!
退后 我们有人质!
We have hostages so back off!
别开枪!
Hold your fire!
来吧 伙计!
Come on man!
我们能过去 走吧
We can make it through. We've got to move.
快走!
Let's go!
快走! 快!
Move! Let's go!
快!
Go!
快走! 快走!
Move it! Move it!
为了达到目的
And in order to do this,
必须储备石油资源
our fossil fuels must be conserved.
金 你把卡尔曼滤波器发给我了吗?
Kim, did you send me that Kalman filter?
什么?
What?
卡尔曼滤波器 我要把那张图清晰化
The Kalman filter, I needed to clean up that image.
见鬼! 我给忘了 在我的工具箱里
Oh, shoot! I forgot about it. It's in my help box.
你怎么能忘? 这是你手头唯一的工作
How can you forget about it? It's the only thing you're working on.
对不起...
I'm sorry, look...
我马上发给你
I'm sending it to you, right now.
好了
Done.
金 不知你脑子在想什么
Kim, I don't know where your head is at,
我们必须在凯尔 辛格勒具有传染性前 找到他
but we need to find Kyle Singer before he's contagious.
别紧张! 我正在尽力
Relax! I'm doing the best I can.
我们要的不是尽力 金.
The best I can isn't what we do around here, Kim.
-是完成任务或者失败  -干嘛对着我说教
-It's either done or it's not.  -So why are you lecturing me,
已经发到你系统里了
it's in your system.
我是考夫曼
Kaufman.
你们怎么了?
Is there a problem?
我只是想确保工作顺利开展...
I just need to make sure things are running smoothly around here...
听着 亚当
Look, Adam.
刚才没时间通知你...
I haven't had the chance to brief you but...
杰克在监狱惹了乱子
Jack created a situation over at the prison.
什么乱子?
What kind of situation?
为了救萨拉扎 引发了监狱暴动
He started a riot to free Salazar.
现在他俩被暴徒抓住了
Now they're caught up in the middle of it.
啊
Wow.
他利用金制作了转移令 跟着引起了这些麻烦
He even used Kim to create a transfer order that started the whole thing.
给她点时间平复吧
So cut her a little slack.
嗯...
Umm...
好的 我明白了
Yeah, okay, I understand.
现在大家的压力都很大
We're all under a lot of pressure here.
在事情不可挽回前 尽快找到凯尔 辛格勒吧
So let's just find Kyle Singer before it's too late.
好的 谢谢你 米歇尔
Yeah, okay. Thanks, Michelle.
凯尔 你在干嘛? 我们没办法逃出去
Kyle, what are you doing? There's no way out of here.
你不应该受到牵连
You don't deserve what happened.
我才是罪有应得
I do.
如果我死了
If I die
病毒也会跟着我死去!
the virus is dying with me!
把脚放到凳子上!
Put your feet up here!
凯尔 坚持住
Kyle, hold on.
噢 凯尔
Oh, Kyle.
"欢迎回家"晚会?
A "Welcome Home" party?
你不该这么做
You shouldn't be doing this.
你什么意思?
What are you talking about?
你掌管着事务
You've been running things.
让拉姆知道你是他的搭档
Show Ramon you're gonna be his partner.
不是为他包办宴会的
Not his caterer.
关你什么事?
Why do you care?
你不是不想卷进我的事务中吗
You don't want to be involved in my business.
不 宝贝 我关心你的
No, puppy, I care about you.
我想让你得到你应得的一切
And I want you to get what you've earned.
-喂?  -是我
-Yes?  -It's me.
骚乱还在继续
Riot's still going on.
但我们知道拉姆还活着
But we know Ramon's alive.
对
Yeah.
但鲍尔很快就能带他出来
But Bauer's got to get him out soon.
反恐局很快就能找出凯尔 辛格勒
CTU is getting close to finding Kyle Singer.
如果被他们找到 拉姆就别想出来了
And if they do, they'll never let Ramon go.
那就别让他们找到辛格勒
Then make sure they don't find Singer.
-我正在想办法  -快去做
-I'm working on it.  -Get it done.
就是他 他是辛格勒
That's him, that's Singer.
那是只枪吗?
Was that a gun?
对
Yeah.
有人抓了他
Someone's got him.
从这张图上看不到卡车的牌照
We're not gonna be able to get the truck's license plate from this shot.
我去调用他们所去方向的交通录相
I'll get access to the traffic cameras in the direction they're heading.
看看能不能再发现他们
See if we can find them again.
我们发现47分钟前 凯尔 辛格勒被人从商场带走了
We found Kyle Singer being driven away from the mall, 47 minutes ago.
你们在查汽车牌照吗?
Are you working up a vehicle ID?
找到此车的相关图像 就能查到
We will, as soon as we're able to get any visual.
这个摄像机出了问题
This camera's damaged. It's malfunctional.
他们肯定带着人质从右边经过
Must have the hostages on the right.
试试转动摄像头
Try and pan the camera over.
会被他们发现的
They may see the camera move.
我们没得选择 快试试
We don't have a choice. Do it.
他们在那儿
There they are.
在他们杀人前 我们必须赶到那儿
We got to get in there before they start killing everyone.
快点! 快点!
Come on! Come on!
快! 快!
Faster! Faster!
让我们折磨这些狱警 直到他们放我们走
Let's start wasting the guards unless they let us walk
敢走出去一步 砰!
First step outside, bang!
脑袋马上开花
Headshot from a sniper.
你知道个屁
You don't know that.
我知道 在奇诺时发生过这样的事
I know, cause that's what went down in Chino
他们才不会管人质死活 因为他们的目的是不让我们出去
They'll let the guard get wasted cause all they care about is keeping us in.
那我们怎么办?
What the hell are we doing here then?
把枪给我
Give me your gun.
带人质过来
Bring them over here.
跟他们玩玩儿
We're gonna have a little fun with them.
让他们跪下
Put them on their knees.
谁不想死?
Who wants to live?
好吧
Okay.
我再问一次
Let's try it again.
-谁不想死?  -我
-Who wants to live?  -Me.
我
I do.
你 过来
Him. Over here.
来吧
Come on.
还有吗?
Who else?
我以前从没见过你
I've never seen you before.
我是新来的
I'm new here.
你 过来
Him. Over here.
六分之一的机会
One in six chance.
你先来
You first.
求你了
Please.
别让我这么做
Don't make me do this man.
很简单的 小杂种
There's nothing to it, you little bitch.
-把枪指着你脑壳  -不!
-Just put the gun to your head.  -I can't!
我不...
I can't...
照我说的做 听见了吗?
You're gonna do it. You hear me?
-照我说的做  -求你了 求你了
-You're gonna do it.  -Please, please.
简单得很 看着?
It's easy, see?
你需要做的只是微笑着...
All you gotta do is smile...
扣动板机
and pull the trigger.
现在还有五分之一的机会
Now it's one in five.
来吧!
Let's go!
不!
No!
不 我做不到...
No, I can't...
做不到...
I can't...
-真浪费时间 杀了他  -等等!
-This is a waste of my time. Shoot him.  -No, wait!
-杀了他!  -等等!
-Shoot him!  -Wait!
来吧 老兄
Come on, man.
照他说的做吧
Just do it.
至少这样你有活下来的机会 是吧?
This way at least you've got a chance, okay?
做吧
Do it.
加油!
Come on!
如果你不做
If you're not gonna do it,
让我们来
we will.
中彩了
We have a winner.
这场好戏 为了这个新来的家伙上演
Let's hear it for the new guy.
我们正在见证着成果
We're now seeing concrete results.
这条路我们会继续走下去
This is a road we will continue to travel.
我找到了另一个路口拍下的图 肯定是那辆车
I got a shot coming in from a camera at the next intersection definitely the same truck.
能看到牌照吗?
Can you read the license plate?
没下载完 还看不到
We won't be able to read anything until it finishes downloading.
我通过系统看到了鉴证科对你父亲
I just saw the IAD inquiry coming over the system
在监狱所做之事的调查
about what you're father's doing at the prison.
他们正在质疑你为他做的那份转移令
They're questioning the transfer you generated for him.
知道了
I heard.
如果你需要我证明 你并不知道他要劫走萨拉扎
If you want me to say that you didn't know he was gonna use it to break out Salazar
我会的
I will.
谢谢 我没事
Thanks. I'll be okay.
等等 停止下载了 显示错误信息
Hold on. It stopped downloading, I'm getting an error message.
错误402...
Error 402 that...
说明内部路由器出了问题
means trouble with the internal router.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
有一个路由器出了问题
There's a problem with one of the routers.
我正在修理
I'm trying to fix it.
你为什么不找技术部
Why don't you call Tech.
不用 我能搞定
No, it's okay.
我想我找到了故障原因
I think I found the problem.
有一条线路断了
Checks on circuit kicked in.
肯定是其中一根电压猛增
Must have been one of the line surge.
现在能用了
Should be up and running now.
有问题来找我
Let me know if you have any more problems.
好
I will.
又可以用了 出了什么问题?
Hey, it's back up. What was it?
不清楚
I'm not sure.
可能是某条线路电压猛增 让路由器短路了?
Is it possible a line surge could have knocked out a router?
不是我造成的 可以问问克萝伊?
Well not from my side, you can ask Chloe?
找到了
Got it.
稍等
Hold on.
我是德斯勒
Dessler.
米歇尔 我们查到了车牌
Michelle, I've got a plate on the pick up.
很好 最后发现它的地点在哪儿?
Good, where do you last have it?
在圣达菲斯普林斯的北部拍到的 正往西方向开去
The shots on the north part of Santa Fe Springs, it was driving west.
好 把它发给警局 让他们去找
Okay, I want you to put this out to mobile units LAPD.
务必全力找到这辆车
I want everyone looking for this vehicle.
好的
Okay, right.
好 瑞恩 继续说
Alright, Ryan, I'm back.
你认为鲍尔劫走萨拉扎是他一个人干的
So do you have any idea if Bauer is trying to break out Salazar on his own
还是有同伙?
or if he is working with someone?
我也正在查这个
I'm trying to figure that out now.
-查到了打给你  -好的
-I'll get back to you when I found out.  -You do that.
什么事 米歇尔?
Yeah, Michelle?
你知道监狱发生的事吗?
Are you following what's going on at the prison?
我刚收到消息 到底发生了什么?
I just saw the update come over. What the hell's happening?
具体情况还不清楚 不过是杰克造成的
We don't have all the details yet but Jack's behind it.
查他的电话和电邮记录
I need you to check his phone logs, e-mail
看他最近调用过的档案文件
See what case files he's accessed recently.
查些什么?
What am I looking for?
任何能帮我们弄清 为什么他这么做的东西
Anything that'll help us figure out why he's doing this.
你确定? 你真的要我去翻他的办公室?
Are you sure? You really want me snooping in his office?
是的
Yes.
好的
You got it.
这里是外科室
Surgery?
我是托尼·阿尔梅达的妻子米歇尔
Yeah, this is Tony Almedia's wife Michelle.
-他怎么样?  -嗯... 我去看看 稍等
-How's he doing?  -Ah... I'll check. One moment please.
-阿尔梅达夫人?  -嗯?
-Mrs. Almeida?  -Yeah?
手术还在进行中
He's still in surgery.
他出来了我们就通知你
You'll be contacted as soon as he's rolled into recovery.
哪个手术室?
What room is he in?
嗯... 4号手术室
Umm... Operating room 4.
-谢谢  -不客气
-Thank you.  -You're welcome.
-网管处 埃文  -呃 埃文 我是米歇尔
-Network ops, Evan.  -Yeah, Evan, it's Michelle.
我们能搞到好人医院的信息资料吗?
Do you know if we get all our feeds from Good Samaritan?
我查一查
Let me check.
可以 你有什么需要?
Yeah, they do. What do you need?
看有没有4号手术室的录像信息
See if they're video docu-ing OR4.
有的 要发到哪儿?
Yeah, they are. Where do you want it?
-发到我桌面上  -好的 稍等
-Send it to my desk top.  -Alright. It'll take a second.
好 发给你了 还有别的事吗?
Right, there you go. Anything else?
-没了 谢谢  -不客气
-No. Thank you.  -Sure.
-四毫米四毫米地来  -增大压力
-Four by four.  -More pressure.
-握住 做吧  -好了
-Hold that down. There you go.  -I've got it.
再拿一支镊子?
Do you have another clamp?
镊子
Clamp.
洗衣房在里面一百码
The laundry room's a hundred yards in.
我到了之后 会找最合适的爆破地点
I'll ID the exact locations for the explosives once we get there.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
长官 准备好了
Sir, we're ready for you.
上面有监视器
Monitor's up.
你能在你的视镜上观看
You should be seeing it on your IPC.
-运行正常  -很好
-It's working.  -Okay.
好的 出发
Alright, let's go.
把无线系统调成静音
Radio silence while we're in there.
一旦被听见 他们可能会杀了所有人质
If they hear us, they might kill everyone.
-收到  -是 长官
-Copy that.  -Yes, sir.
出发
Let's go.
好的!
Alright!
第二轮!
Round two!
你来
Then you.
我是囚犯 不是警卫
I'm a prisoner, not a guard.
我是拉姆·萨拉扎
I'm Ramon Salazar.
-你肯定听说过我  -换一个人吧
-I'm sure you've heard of me.  -You should pick someone else,
他说的是真的
he's telling you the truth.
他被关进隔离区不到一星期
He's just transferred to cell block less than a week ago.
我是联邦探员 我正护送他离开监狱
I'm a federal agent, I was escorting him out of the prison.
所以你没见过我们
That's why you've never seen us here before.
很好
Good.
联邦探员
Federal agent.
报上名来?
What's your name?
好啊
Alright.
原来是杰克探员
It's gonna be Agent Jack
抓捕拉姆·萨拉扎的那个
against Ramon Salazar.
最后一战!
A battle to the finish!
来吧 杰克
Come on, Jack.
给这外国佬做个示范
Show this foreigner how it's done.
如果我死了
If I die,
-我兄弟不会放过你  -闭嘴!
-my brother will find you.  -Shut up!
来吧!
Do it!
好了
Alright.
又轮到你了
You're up.
看来你运气到头了 杰克
Looks like your mother's a title, Jack.
拉姆 卧倒!
Ramon, stay down!
快走!
Come on!
安全了! 别开枪!
All clear! Hold your fire!
我没多大成就
I have no triumphs.
只有挫败
Only defeats.
上帝啊!
God!
-实验室  -我是克萝伊·奥布莱恩
-Lab.  -This is Chloe O'Brian.
我在杰克的办公室
I'm in Jack's office.
请带毒品工具箱上来?
Could you send someone up the drug kit, please?
马上
It's on its way.
事情的区别很明显
The differences on the issues are clear.
但我相信你并没有选择政纲
But I believe you don't elect a platform.
你选择了一个人
You elect a man.
我对总统你
And I am frankly troubled
从私人角度做选择 并会继续从私人角度做选择
by some of the personal choices that this president has made
感到很担忧
and continues to make.
我们都知道
We're all aware of the allegations
你前妻受到过指控
and indictments surrounding the President's former wife.
大多数人都相信
Most of us have operated under the assumption
你已有了前车之鉴
that the President will not repeat his history
不会再任用道德上有问题的人
of associating with the persons of questionable moral character.
但是
However,
我的团队刚了解到
my office has just learned
和总统你有瓜葛的一个女人
that the woman with whom the President is currently involved,
安妮 帕卡德医生
Doctor Anne Packard
被控蓄意伪造医药检测书
is being accused of helping to fabricate the results of a clinical drug trial.
这种药品夺去了三条无辜的生命
A drug which later led to the deaths of three innocent people.
你这样不道德
This is outrageous.
辩论场不是法院 也不是小报
This debate is not a court of law nor is it a tabloid paper.
你不能在 此时 此地
This is neither the time nor the place
对一个公民发起人身攻击
to launch a personal attack on a private citizen.
总统阁下
Mr. President
参议员还有30秒时间 先生 请继续
the Senator still has 30 more seconds. Sir, please.
现在正是最好的时间
This is exactly the right time.
因为我相信 国家领导人在生活中做出的决定
Because I believe the choices your leaders make in their own lives
影响他代表人民所做出的决定
reflect the choices that they will make on your behalf.
所以我还是要问
And so the question remains.
是总统知晓她的罪状 但选择了视而不见?
Did the President know of these accusations and choose to ignore them?
还是在重复以前犯下的过错?
Or is he repeating past mistakes once again?
总统阁下 请反驳
Mr. President your rebuttal.
我非常自信地告诉大家
I can tell you with complete confidence
参议员的指控 是错误的
that the Senator's accusation is false.
参议员在转移今天应该讨论的辩题
And that I believe it is the Senator's way of aborting the issues at hand.
今晚 我是来讨论我国面临的最紧要问题
Now I came here tonight to discuss the real issues pressing our country.
上帝啊
Oh, god.
-我认为参议员在...  -你明白了吧?
-I assume that the Senator was...  -Now do you get it?
我认为此事不应该被忽视或遗忘
I do not believe this is something to be swept under the rug and forgotten.
阳性
It's positive.
我去告诉米歇尔
I'll go tell Michelle.
克萝伊 你在我爸办公室干嘛?
Chloe, what are you doing in my dad's office?
米歇尔让我检查你爸的东西
Michelle wanted me to go through your dad's stuff.
为什么?
Why?
找找能帮我们了解他行为的东西
To find anything that can help us understand what he's doing.
有事吗?
What's up?
你那边会不会电压猛增 导致路由器关闭
I wanted to know if a line surge could shut down a router on your side of the ITS room.
不会 我的电压保护器在楼上 没在我办公室
No, my circuit protectors are upstairs. Not in my ITS.
怎么了?
Why?
应该没什么
Ah, it's probably nothing.
你找到什么没?
Did you find anything?
我不能跟你谈
I can't talk about this.
为什么 我可以帮忙啊
Why not, maybe I can help.
你帮不了 走开 好吗?
You can't help so just go, okay?
箱子里是什么?
What's in the box?
要拿去给米歇尔看的东西
Just stuff I'm taking to Michelle.
你这样问很没规矩 金
This is really an inappropriate behavior, Kim.
你反应过度了吧 克萝伊? 我...
Why are you doing this, Chloe? I mean...
我只是想帮你
I'm just trying to help you.
你帮不了 我没必要在这儿跟你说话
You can't help. And I don't have to have this conversation.
外勤条例中 有一项规定
Under field op mandate, there's a regulation.
40或41条规定 我有管辖特权
I believe it's 40 or 41 that says that I have jurisdictional prerogative.
你快走开吧?
So could you just leave?
除非你告诉我箱子里有什么
Not until you tell me what's in the box.
我认为你爸在吸毒
I think your dad's been using drugs.
-什么?  -好吧
-What?  -That's right.
橡胶止血带
Rubber tourniquet,
注射器
syringe.
刚做了鸦片测试 阳性
We just had the vials tested of opiates, It was positive.
他举止怪异 对吗?
He's been acting really weird. Okay?
你真不该逼我这样做
It's really not fair you made me do this.
我很不舒服
It's very uncomfortable.
杰克的文件中没什么发现 不过有东西你得看看
I didn't find anything in Jack's records but there is something you need to see.
你在他办公室发现这个?
You found this in his office?
给你看之前 我得搞清楚这是什么东西
I wanted to make sure what it was before I showed you.
瓶中的液体 做了鸦片测试 阳性
The liquid in these vials tested positive for opiates.
可能是海洛因
Probably heroine.
我觉得杰克在吸毒
I think Jack's a user.
找到了
I got it.
巡警发现了载过凯尔 辛格勒的卡车
A patrol car just found the truck Kyle Singer was in
停在富勒工业中心 第四区 2000栋
parked in a industrial complex in Fuller and fourth 2000 block.
马上通知队伍待命
Pipe these into the teams on standby.
就当那里的每个人都有传染性 设为一级传染状态
Assume everyone on the site is contagious and use level 1 CDC protocol.
找到他!
Let's get him!
见鬼!
Damn!
还有别的出口吗?
Is there any other way out?
没有 我们被锁在里面了
No, we're pinned in.
我们应该料到这些情况
We must have known this could happen.
该怎么办 杰克?
What's the plan, Jack?
把枪给我
Give me the shotgun.
脱下制服
Take off your uniform.
去年我和我的内阁 致力于一个总体的学术规划
I have worked the past year with my administration on my overall academic plan.
效果不怎么好
The projection could not look better.
-我是德斯勒  -我是考吉尔
-Dessler.  -This is Cowgil.
正在靠近富勒工业中心
Approaching the industrial complex on Fuller.
有三个仓库
There are three warehouses on the property.
我看看能不能用红外线缩小目标范围
I'll see if we can narrow it down with infrared.
收到
Roger.
亚当 能不能用红外线卫星瞄准工业中心
Adam, see if you can pull up an infrared satellite on the industrial complex.
好
On it.
金 登陆NHA服务器
Kim, log into the NHA server.
找找那儿有没有合适的卫星
We need to see if they have any satellites in position.
好
Okay.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
我没事
Nothing, I'm fine.
我们搜了整个区 没发现杰克和萨拉扎
We just swept these blocks. There's no sign of Jack or Salazar.
我在冲击区安排了一只小队
Look I got a team in the assault block.
封锁区域后 他们才能进行正常搜索
They can't do a proper search until we lock it down.
那要花掉半小时
That can take up to a half hour.
如果你想逃脱
If you want to get out of this thing,
你就要相信我
you gonna have to trust me.
一切都照我说的做
And do everything that I tell you.
明白吗?
You understand?
好吧
Alright.
-来吧 我们走  -嗯 我想这么干
-Come on, let's go.  -Okay, here's what I want you to do.
我要你们到直升飞机上 查看周边情况
I want you to take that chopper and I want you sweep the perimeter.
-你在干嘛 杰克?  -让这些人退开
-What are you doing, Jack?  -You get these people to move back.
不然你就把我放倒
Or you're gonna have to take me out.
我们要那架直升飞机
We need that chopper.
别这样
Don't do this.
我和米歇尔谈过了
I just spoke with Michelle,
我们马上就找到凯尔 辛格勒了
we're close to getting Kyle Singer.
这次马上起不了作用
Close ain't gonna cut it this time.
我要去交送萨拉扎 马上!
I gotta deliver Salazar now!
我不会让你走的 杰克!
I'm not letting you go, Jack!
要多久才能找到凯尔 辛格勒?
How long is it gonna take to find Kyle Singer?
半小时? 一小时?
A half an hour? An hour?
我要用飞机运送萨拉扎 在60秒内搞定
I gotta get Salazar in the air, in that chopper in the next 60 seconds.
否则成千上万的人会死去
Or hundred thousand people will die.
-让他走  -让他走?
-Let him go.  -Let him go?
让他走
Let him go.
我们会跟踪直升机 让你的人听指挥 典狱长
We'll track the chopper. I need you to keep your people under control, Warden.
拜托了
Please.
我不能让萨拉扎出事
I can't have anything happen to Salazar.
好吧
Alright.
我是典狱长米切尔 全体人员退后
This is Warden Mitchell, I want all teams to stand down.
重复 放弃警戒!
I repeat, stand down!
鲍尔探员要带萨拉扎上直升飞机
Agent Bauer will take Salazar to the SWAT chopper.
所有人员注意 后退待命
I want a conformation from all teams on the stand down order.
让他用直升飞机
Let him take the chopper.
放弃警戒
Stand down.
好了? 退后
Alright? Back off.
好了 杰克
Alright, Jack.
没人会阻止你了
No one's gonna try and stop you.
让这些人退后 放下武器
Get these men to back off and holster their weapons.
退后! 放弃警戒!
Back off! Stand down!
让他过去!
Let them through!
走吧
Let's go.
-让他们放下武器  -放下武器!
-Get them to holster their weapons.  -Holdster your weapons!
-放下武器!  -退后!
-Lower your weapon!  -Stand down!
让狙击手放下枪 下来 快!
Get the snipers down, off the roof, now!
-快!  -快下来 快下来!
-Now!  -Off the roof! Get off the roof!
退后!
Back off!
照他说的做!
Do what he says!
找到辛格勒 还有另一个人
We have Singer plus one.
总部 找到辛格勒和另一个人
Center, Singer plus one.
他在干嘛?
What's he doing?
摧毁飞机定位器
Disabling or calming the locator.
喂?
Yes?
蔡斯 我是米歇尔 找到凯尔 辛格勒了
Chase, it's Michelle. We have Kyle Singer.
听不见
I can't hear you.
找到凯尔 辛格勒了
We found Kyle Singer.
-找到了凯尔?!  -是的!
-We've got Kyle?!  -Yes!
杰克 找到凯尔 辛格勒了!
Jack, we found Kyle Singer!
总统阁下 你可以整晚都谈事实和数据
You can talk about facts or figures all night, Mr. President.
再说一次
Once again
我认为这是一个关于判断力和诚实的问题
I see this as a question of judgment and integrity.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
比起我 你成了你们国家更大的敌人
Now you are an even bigger enemy to your country than me.